 [
   {
     "qno": 1,
"question": "What is the value of 3^2+4^2?",
"opa": "12",
"opb": " 25",
"opc": "21 ",
"opd": "20 ",
"correctanswer": "2"
},
   {
     "qno": 2,
"question": " If a = 2, b = 3, what is the value of a^2+2ab+b^2? ",
"opa": " 25",
"opb": " 20",
"opc": " 36",
"opd": " 49",
"correctanswer": "1"
},
   {
     "qno": 3,
"question": "Solve: 5x-2=3x+6 ",
"opa": "4 ",
"opb": "5 ",
"opc": " 3",
"opd": "6 ",
"correctanswer": "1"
},
   {
     "qno": 4,
"question": "  What is the square root of 81?",
"opa": " 8",
"opb": "5 ",
"opc": "7 ",
"opd": "9 ",
"correctanswer": "4"
},
   {
     "qno": 5,
"question": "Simplify: 3(2x+4)−2(x−1) ",
"opa": " 4x+14 ",
"opb": " 6x+5",
"opc": " 19x-x",
"opd": " 4x-14",
"correctanswer": "1"
},
  {
"qno": 6,
"question": "What is the LCM of 6 and 8?",
"opa": "12",
"opb": "24",
"opc": "18",
"opd": "48",
"correctanswer": "2 "
},
{
"qno": 7,
"question": "What is the sum of 234 and 156?",
"opa": "390",
"opb": "380",
"opc": "400",
"opd": "370",
"correctanswer": "390"
},
{
"qno": 8,
"question": "How many sides does a triangle have?",
"opa": "2",
"opb": "3",
"opc": "4",
"opd": "5",
"correctanswer": "2"
},
{
"qno": 9,
"question": "What is the place of 5 in 3,582?",
"opa": "500",
"opb": "50",
"opc": "5",
"opd": "5,000",
"correctanswer": "1"
},
{
"qno": 10,
"question": "What is the 3/4 of 20?",
"opa": "10",
"opb": "12",
"opc": "14",
"opd": "15",
"correctanswer": "4"
},
{
"qno": 11,
"question": "Which unit is used to measure length?",
"opa": "Kilogram",
"opb": "Litre",
"opc": "Metre",
"opd": "Degree",
"correctanswer": "3"
},
{
"qno": 12,
"question": "What is the value of 15 ÷ 3 + 2 x 4? ",
"opa": "10",
"opb": "11",
"opc": "12",
"opd": "13",
"correctanswer": "4"
},
{
"qno": 13,
"question": "Simplify(4 + 6) x 2",
"opa": "16",
"opb": "20",
"opc": "18",
"opd": "20",
"correctanswer": "2"
} 
 ]
    
